

Profile

8+ years of experience as a Web/Mobile app developer. Client-focused and detail-oriented programmer with strong software engineering backgrounds. Working on Web/Mobile development industry, I have got rich experience in building professional websites. Mainly full-stack Web development using Angular, React, Vue and more. I like teamwork since it's very helpful for engineers.

Employment History

Marketing Specialist at Facebook

September 2017 — January 2018

 Responsible for the management of Facebook clients' social media platforms, campaigns, and advertising campaigns.

Web developer as N3

February 2018 — February 2020

- Worked as a effective and positive team member to code, test, report, and launchoperations.
- · Managed front-end and back-end development.
- Successfullyidentified, diagnosed, and fixed website problems, including broken links, typographical errors, and formatting issues.
- Helpedto achieve a consistent look and visual theme across the website by promoting uniform fonts, formatting, images, and layout.
- · Worked to assess competing websites in regards to content, look, and feel.
- Evaluated and became knowledgeable in new standards, technologies, and trends in website development.

Education

Computer Science, Griffith College

April 2013 — April 2015

1 References

Details

monkeyd.luffy192020@gmail.c

live:.cid.44094721cee87efc

Links

React Health Care Website Angular Food Delivery Website

Skills

React

VueJS

Angular Node

React Native

Leadership and Teamwork

Languages

English

Hobbies

Football, Tennis, Swimming, Snowboarding, billiards